

ALEXANDR KOZHEVNIKOV

SENIOR FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER / iOS DEVELOPER

SKILLS

PHP
Yii2

VueJS

PostgreSQL

MySQL

Swift (Cocoa)

• • • • •

WHAT ELSE



CONTACT

Site: https://kozhevnikov.site
Github: https://github.com/onmotion

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/al
exandr-kozhevnikov-73b99a116

exandr-kozhevnikov-/3b99a116

alexandr@kozhevnikov.site
onmotion1@gmail.com

Saint-Petersburg, Russian Federation

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Web Developer

SKL Group | Nov 2015 - Present

- Development and support of web services and web apps
- iOS development
- Web servers administration
- DevOps

Stock Administrator

Technosila | Jun 2009 - Oct 2015

- Organization of the warehouse

EDUCATION

Saint Petersburg State University of Aerospace and Instrumentation

2013 - 2018 | Computer Science and Engineering (bachelors)

Site: http://suai.ru

Bryukhovets Agrarian College

2004-2007 | Economics (Associate's degree)

Site: http://bak93.ru

MAIN INTERESTS

- Coding
- UI/UX
- Fitness
- Computer science

OPENSOURCE EXPERIENCE

Yii2 charts widget

Oct 2018

Github: https://github.com/onmotion/yii2-widget-apexcharts

Telegram support Bot for Yii2

Aug 2016

Github: https://github.com/onmotion/yii2-

telegram

Yii2 Gallery module

Feb 2016

Github: https://github.com/onmotion/yii2-

gallery

OPENSOURCE EXPERIENCE

2/2

iOS ASViewController Feb 2018

Github: https://github.com/onmotion/ASViewController

Yii2 page assessment extension

Sep 2018

Github: https://github.com/onmotion/yii2-page-assessments

Survey module for Yii2 application

Oct 2018

Github: https://github.com/onmotion/yii2-survey

ABOUT

My name is Alexandr and I am a Full Stack web developer with an overall experience of about 5 years.

I am in love with my job and I am hungry for new skills and technologies. I like to work on interesting projects and meet interesting people. Workaholic and perfectionist.

I have a lot of experience with *PHP* (mostly *Yii2*), as well as client *JS*. Recently, I love using *Vue2* (*Nuxt SSR*) and a *microservice architecture* pattern with *queues* in my projects. For the database, I use both *PostgreSQL* (primarily) and *MySQL*. There is also experience with *Swift* as an *iOS* app (it is in the App Store).

I fully understand how a modern web works and how to make a web application not only fast but also convenient. I love UNIX-based systems and have plenty of experience with *Debian* and *MacOS*. SOLID, DRY, KISS it's not only a set of letters for me.

...everything that can be automated should be automated.

